原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     屯栗子  布塔  不见19  glida
翻译     kathy567  TracyOY  王木木
翻译     岩菌  海云生  辰星晓Reginamoon
时间轴     西·查  知之  没有影子
时间轴     想念Gallifrey的wholock  Ans
校对     布塔
后期     渔夫
总监     布塔
系紧了  快点
Tie it off, come on!
伙计们  伙计们  我们还是回去吧
Hey, guys! Guys, I think we should turn back.
放着钱不赚  休想
And lose good money? Not a chance.
跟紧点
Stay close.
到了
Here we are.
踩他上去
Get on his back.
快点
Hurry up.
他在那里  去抓他
There he is. Go get him.
我会让你付出代价的
Oh, you'll pay for that.
不要  不要  求你
No. No, please.
求你了  不要
Please, no.
站住
Hold it there.
我只抓到一只...
I only got one...
但他是个好样本
but he's a fine specimen.
-就这点  -对
- That's all? - Yeah.
那蘑菇咬了我两次
That shroom bit me twice.
彼岸花
Tomb Bloom.
很久很久以前
Once upon a time...
很久很久以前又一次
or perhaps twice upon a time,
你们可能还记得这个故事
for you may remember this story...
有一位叫玛琳菲森的强大仙子
there was a powerful Fey named Maleficent.
沉睡魔咒2：恶魔夫人
出于某些原因  这位恶魔夫人
For some reason, the mistress of evil
摩尔王国的守护者
and protector of the Moors...
过了这么久  依旧被人憎恶
was still hated after all this time.
的确  她对奥萝拉公主施过咒
True, she had cursed the princess, Aurora...
但那时的她还没有发现
but that was before she found light
人类孩童心中的善良之光
in the heart of a human child...
也还没有将她视如己出抚养长大
and raised the girl as her own.
毕竟  正是玛琳菲森的爱
After all, it was Maleficent's love
解开了那个诅咒
which broke that very same curse.
但这个细节却不知怎地被人遗忘了
But that detail was somehow mysteriously forgotten.
而王国里始终流传着的
For as the tale was told
被人一遍又一遍重复的故事
over and again throughout the kingdom...
是玛琳菲森又一次做了恶人
Maleficent became the villain once more.
时候到了  来吧  把大家都叫来
It's time, guys. Come on. Let's get everyone.
今天可是大日子
It's the big day!
-来吧  -走吧
- Come on. - Let's go!
醒醒  醒醒
Wake up. Wake up.
快来呀
Come on.
快点  泥沼精  时候到了
Hurry up, wallerbogs! It's time!
你们俩还记得秘密计划吗
Do you both remember the secret plan?
全在脑袋里呢
I've got it all right here.
我什么时候把秘密告诉给女王
When do I tell the queen the secret?
你必须得耐心点  绿蕨仙子
You must be patient, Thistlewit.
你们觉得奥萝拉女王醒了吗
Do you think Queen Aurora's awake yet?
反正她已经不是"睡美人"了
Well, she's not "Sleeping Beauty" anymore.
我听懂你这个双关了
I see what you did there.
接下来要讨论的是  仙子失踪
Next item of business, the missing fairies.
我已经派出更多精灵去搜寻彼岸花园了
I've sent more sprites to search the Tomb Bloom field.
傍晚时分他们会来汇报进展
They'll report back to me at nightfall.
在找到他们之前我们会继续搜寻
We will keep searching until we find them.
请别对我举树枝表达不满  叶夫
Please don't raise your roots at me, Lief.
用你的躯干碾压人类没有用
Crushing humans with branches is not going to help.
迪瓦尔  你应该站在我这边的
Diaval, you're supposed to be on my side.
我是摩尔王国的女王  我就是人类
Well, I'm Queen of the Moors, and I am a human.
我们须得学会心存一点善意
We must all learn a little kindness.
别挡道
Coming through.
借过
Excuse us.
官方精灵事务
Official pixie business.
借一步说话  陛下
A word, Your Majesty.
-或者借两步  -姑母们
- Maybe two. - Aunties...
你们得跟其他人一样等轮到自己再说
you need to wait your turn like everyone else.
不行  这件事不能等  女王陛下
No! This can't wait, Your Grace.
片刻不容
Not for a moment.
不然我就要炸了  我真的会炸
Or I might burst. Truly, I might.
那不是...
Is that...?
宾托
Pinto!
她带了礼物来
She's come bearing gifts.
暖树上的第一滴树汁
The first sap from the warming trees.
为了大日子准备的
It's for the big day!
闭嘴  绿蕨仙子
Quiet, Thistlewit.
什么大日子
What big day?
我的王冠
My crown!
我没心情陪你们逗趣
I'm not in the mood for this.
宾托
Pinto!
行了
Come on.
你们要去哪里  姑母们
Where are you going, aunties?
我没时间跟你玩  宾托
I don't have time for games, Pinto.
你们到底怎么回事
What's gotten into all of you?
她去那边了  陛下
There she goes, Your Majesty.
快回来
Come back here.
宾托  今天玩够了吧
Pinto. I've had enough of your games for today.
看我成什么样了
Look at me.
菲利普  你来做什么
Philip. What are you doing here?
我在找你
I was looking for you.
-你好吗  -你好
- Oh, well, hello. - Hello.
真的很抱歉  我现在没空跟你聊天
I'm really sorry, I can't talk right now.
摩尔王国一片混乱
The Moors have turned to madness.
我有一大堆投诉要处理
I've got a castle full of complaints.
我知道你有多忙
I know how busy you are.
我本想问你件事
I wanted to ask you something.
问吧
Yes.
你觉得奥斯戴王国和摩尔王国有可能结盟吗
Do you think there could be a union between Ulstead and the Moors?
结盟
A union?
将两地连接起来
To connect both lands.
带来和谐与和平
To bring harmony and peace.
我想可以架起一座桥
I've been imagining a bridge.
一座桥
Oh, a bridge.
没错  一座桥
Yes, a bridge.
结盟是个好主意...
A union's a wonderful idea...
如果双方同意的话
if both sides are willing.
这个嘛  我正在努力
Well, I'm working on that part.
他要搞砸了
He's going to blow it.
给他点时间  他还在热身
Give him time. He's warming up.
等等
Wait.
你今天穿得好正式
That's your formal coat.
你们都有份参与  对吧
You're in on all of this, aren't you?
如果你忙的话  我可以之后再来
If you're busy, I could always come back.
不不  不用
No. No, no.
我完全不忙
I'm not busy at all.
可是我不想...
No, because I'd hate to...
真的  我有空
Really. All ears.
你想说什么
What did you want to talk about?
你说得对  他要搞砸了
You're right. He's blowing it.
五年前  我以为自己永远失去你了
Five years ago, I thought I lost you forever.
我决定改变这一天的意义
I've decided to reclaim this day for us.
我对你一见钟情
I've loved you since the moment I met you
日渐情深
and every day since.
如果世间有真爱  那我找到了
If love has a truth, here is mine.
没有任何魔法或诅咒
There is no magic nor curse
能把我从你身边分开  奥萝拉
that could ever tear me away from you, Aurora.
你确定现在方便吗
Are you sure this is a good time?
菲利普
Oh, Philip.
他跪下了
He's on his knee.
他可真够磨蹭的
He took his sweet time about it.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.
-愿意  -愿意
- Yes? - Yes.
我愿意  快起来吻我
Yes! Yes, just stand up. Kiss me.
我们要办婚礼了
We're having a wedding!
秘密惊喜婚礼
A secret surprise wedding.
当然了  我们要告诉双方家长
Of course, we have to tell our parents.
一定要吗
Do we?
夫人
Mistress.
什么事
What?
我有个消息
I have a little bit of news.
那就说吧
Well, on with it.
不是什么大事
It's nothing of any real consequence...
绝对不必反应过激
and it's certainly no reason to overreact.
只不过是
It's just that...
菲利普王子...
Prince Philip has, um...
失踪了
Disappeared?
不是  菲利普...
No. No. Philip has...
染上黄热病了  不  等等
Yellow fever? No, wait!
得麻风病了
Leprosy!
不是  夫人
No, Mistress.
菲利普王子向奥萝拉求...
Prince Philip has asked Aurora if she'll become his...
不要
Don't...
毁了我的早晨
ruin my morning.
夫人  拜托
Mistress, please.
冷静点
Stay calm!
告诉我  殿下
So, tell me, sire...
我要当伴郎吗
am I to be a best man,
还是说您从摩尔找了个怪物伴郎
or did you choose a creature from the Moors?
将军  如果你想打听
General, if that's your way of asking me
她有没有答应
if she said yes, then I, uh...
我知道她答应了  殿下
I know she said yes, sire.
哪个人类不想离开那个鬼地方
What human wouldn't want to leave that place?
你对摩尔居民有什么不满吗  珀西瓦尔
What do you have against Moor folk, Percival?
"摩尔居民"  要这么称呼他们吗
"Moor folk"? Is that what we're calling them now?
长翅膀的野兽  凶残的树木
Winged beasts, murderous trees.
注意言辞  将军
Guard your tongue, General.
你对他们一无所知
You know nothing about them.
我知道玛琳菲森杀人如麻
I know that Maleficent is a killer of men...
毁灭军队  故事大家都知道
destroyer of armies. Or so the story goes.
她不是那样的
She's not like that.
保护这个王国是我的职责
It's my job to protect this kingdom.
老朋友  我会尽职尽责
And I will do so, old friend...
毫不犹豫
without hesitation.
走吧
Walk on.
开门
Open the gates!
陛下  吞并中部的
Your Majesty, spoils from the annexation
战利品送达了
of the Midlands have arrived.
是武器
Weapons.
不  我们不需要武器
No. We have no need of arms.
我们征战的日子结束了
Our days of war are over.
英格瑞斯
Ingrith...
看到我给你留的位置了吧
you see where I've had you placed.
就在我身后
Right behind me.
我永远都会在你身后
And that's where I'll always be.
英格瑞斯  我说了不需要武器
Ingrith, I said we had no need of arms.
有备无患
One can never be too careful.
陛下  弩上弦了
Your Majesty, it's cocked.
是吗
Is it, now?
-父亲  母亲  -怎么样
- Father, Mother. - Well?
她怎么说
What did she say?
她答应了
She said yes.
太好了
Yes!
真是天大的好消息
That is wonderful news.
两个王国终于团结一致了
Two kingdoms united at last. Yes.
太好了
Yes.
也许我太自私了
Perhaps I've been selfish...
对此事的看法有错
looking at this the wrong way.
你已经做出了选择
You've made your choice.
现在该庆祝了
Now is a time to celebrate.
很高兴你终于认可了
I'm glad you finally approve.
不仅如此
Much more than that.
我准备热情欢迎你的未婚妻
I am ready to welcome your fiancee with open arms.
她要来参加晚宴
She shall come to dinner.
那太好了
That would be incredible.
但有一个条件
Under one condition.
她要带上她的教母
She will bring her godmother.
陛下  我强烈...
Your Majesty, I strongly...
我们要在这座城堡里
We will meet the one who raised her
见一见养育她的教母
right here in this castle.
没错  王后说得对
Yes. The queen is right.
我不确定她的教母会不会...
I'm not sure her godmother will...
我坚持如此
No, but I insist.
毕竟  我们马上就要成为一家人了
After all, we will soon be family.
通知全国上下
Well, let it be known throughout the kingdom...
我儿子要娶奥萝拉了
that my son is to marry Aurora.
并且玛琳菲森要来参加晚宴
And Maleficent is coming to dinner.
我马上传话下去
I shall send word straightaway.
来了
Incoming.
抓住裙子别放
Hold on to your petticoats!
看啊
Well, well.
怎么样
So?
So.
教母
Godmother...
菲利普向我求婚了
Philip asked me to marry him.
真可怜
Poor thing.
他会缓过来的
He'll recover.
我答应他了
My answer was yes.
-不行  -行
- No. - Yes.
不行
No.
我没有征求你的意见
I wasn't really asking.
我也没有
Nor was I.
你要怎么做
What's next?
把他变成山羊吗
You'll turn him into a goat?
别闹了
Stop.
你为什么不喜欢菲利普
Why don't you like Philip?
首先  他是人类
Well, for one thing, he's human.
我也是人类
I'm a human.
我从没因为这点而针对过你
And I have never held that against you.
直到我坠入爱河
Until I fell in love.
爱情未必会结局圆满  小怪物
Love doesn't always end well, Beasty.
你要知道菲利普可是一位王子
I'll have you know Prince Philip is a prince.
一位非常英俊有魅力的王子
A very handsome and charming prince.
求求你相信我
I'm just asking you to trust me.
给他一个机会
Please give him a chance.
让我们证明你是错的
Let us prove you wrong.
菲利普很善良
Philip is thoughtful...
很体贴
he's very kind...
体什么
Kind of what?
国王和王后邀请我们母女
The king and queen are celebrating tonight...
今晚去城堡参加庆祝晚宴
and they have invited both of us to the castle.
你想让我见他父母
You want me to meet his parents?
只是顿晚餐而已
It's just a dinner.
奥斯戴王国不欢迎我
They don't want me in Ulstead.
为什么我还要去
Why on earth would I go?
因为他母亲想见一见我母亲
Because his mother wishes to meet mine.
求你了
Please.
菲利普
Philip.
我想让你今晚佩戴这个
I want you to wear this tonight.
你的宝剑
Your sword?
因为你的缘故
Because of you,
奥斯戴王国和摩尔王国终于可以团结一致
Ulstead and the Moors will be united at last.
父亲  我对奥萝拉的爱不夹杂任何政治因素
Father, my love for Aurora has nothing to do with politics.
没错  但你们的爱情
Yes, but your love...
可以确保世世代代和平共处
will ensure peace for generations.
拿着它  佩戴上
Now take it. And wear it...
提醒自己我们再也无需兵戎相见
to know that you will never have to use it.
我的孩子
Oh, my son.
我从未感到如此自豪
I've never been more proud.
母亲那边怎么样
And what about Mother?
她能接受吗
Is she okay with this?
你母亲会学着爱上你爱的人
Your mother will learn to love who you love.
彼岸花  彼岸花
Tomb Bloom. Tomb Bloom.
我要失去耐心了
I'm losing my patience.
陛下
Your Majesty.
你得加快进度  马屁精
You need to move faster, Lickspittle.
遵命  陛下
Yes, Your Majesty.
奥萝拉答应了求婚
Aurora said yes.
一切即将完美
It's all coming together...
上演
perfectly.
你好
Hello.
试试别露太多尖牙
Try it with a little less fang.
这样如何
How's this?
练练问好
Try the greeting.
非常感谢你今晚的邀请
How kind of you to invite me this evening.
记住  这不是威胁
Remember, it's not a threat.
非常感谢你今晚的邀请
So very kind of you to invite me this evening.
这样好多了
Yeah. Better.
加上屈膝礼试试
Try it with a curtsy.
不加也挺好的
We can skip that part.
她真的很爱那个小伙子
She really loves that boy, you know.
你这样做是对她的体贴
You're doing her a great kindness.
体贴
Kindness?
夫人
Mistress...
她很漂亮吧
Doesn't she look lovely?
我有东西要给你
I have something for you.
遮住你的角
For your horns.
我觉得这样应该会
I just thought it might make
让菲利普的家人更自在些
Philip's family feel more comfortable.
你也更自在些
And you, as well.
也许是个馊主意
Maybe it's a bad idea.
不
No, it's...
没关系
It's all right.
我太兴奋了
I'm so excited.
我都快受不了了
It's more than I can bear.
是玛琳菲森
It's Maleficent!
干草叉
Pitchforks?
人类真可笑
Humans are hilarious.
有进步
It's getting better.
擅离岗位者死
Anyone leaves their post gets hung.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
他们到了
They're here.
你考虑过把我变成熊吗
Have you ever considered turning me into a bear?
我觉得我当熊肯定很厉害
I think I'd make quite an impressive one.
看看这利爪  太强壮了
Look at their claws. They're so strong.
你说熊干什么
Why are we talking about bears?
有请摩尔王国的奥萝拉女王
Presenting Queen Aurora of the Moors.
谢谢
Thank you.
你看起来美极了
You look wonderful.
能来这里我很高兴
I'm so happy to be here.
奥萝拉  见到你是莫大的荣幸
Aurora, this is truly an honor.
欢迎来到奥斯戴
Welcome to Ulstead.
真是个美丽的姑娘
Such a beautiful girl.
我明白你是怎么偷走菲利普的心了
I can see how you stole Philip's heart.
陛下
Your Majesty.
你头发上的花朵
The flowers in your hair.
我过敏
I'm allergic.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不不不  没关系
Oh, no. No, no. It's all right.
花朵很美
They're beautiful.
有请玛琳菲森
Presenting Maleficent.
玛琳菲森  很高兴再次见到你
Maleficent, it's wonderful to see you again.
这是我父亲  奥斯戴王国的约翰国王
This is my father, King John of Ulstead.
还有我母亲  英格瑞斯王后
And my mother, Queen Ingrith.
欢迎来我们家
Welcome to our home.
非常感谢你今晚的邀请
It's so very kind of you to invite me this evening.
别笑
Don't smile.
我想为你们引见迪亚瓦
And I would like to introduce you to Diaval.
找到这座城堡应该不太麻烦吧
I trust you had no trouble finding the castle.
为什么会有麻烦
Why would I have trouble?
他在和你闲聊
He's making small talk.
我晚点给你解释
I'll explain it later.
完全没有麻烦
No trouble at all.
国王和王后陛下  女士们先生们
Your Majesties, ladies and gentlemen,
晚宴准备好了
dinner is served.
请不要拘束
Please, make yourselves at home.
鸟
Bird.
美味
Delicious.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
餐具是铁的
It's iron.
陛下  就像你对花敏感
Majesty, as you are sensitive to flowers,
她厌恶铁
she is averse to iron.
我不知道
I had no idea.
立刻拿下去
Take it away at once.
你应该觉得用手更自在吧
I trust you'll be comfortable using your hands?
最近天气真暖和  不是吗
Such a warm spell of weather, isn't it?
确实是
It certainly is.
我们为菲利普和奥萝拉准备了一份小礼物
Well, we have a small gift for Philip and Aurora...
庆贺他们在一起的美好未来
to celebrate their glorious future together.
我等不及再次有小孩子在城堡里跑来跑去
I simply can't wait to have a little one running through the castle again.
这座城堡吗
This castle?
是的  当然
Yes, of course.
这里会是他们的家
This will be their home.
我听说奥萝拉有自己的城堡
I hear Aurora has a castle of her own.
是的  陛下
Yes, sir, I do.
好吧  我...
Yes... I'm...
我很好奇
I'm curious.
奥萝拉是怎么成为摩尔王国女王的
How did Aurora become Queen of the Moors?
我让她当的
I made her queen.
她的城堡相当漂亮  你一定得去看看
Her castle is quite stunning. You must see it.
好吧  但事实上  她有另一座城堡
Yes, but in fact, she has another castle.
不是吗
Does she not?
母亲
Mother...
一个在摩尔王国
One in the Moors,
一个她父王留下的
and one left behind by her father.
斯特凡国王的城堡  不是吗
King Stefan, was it not?
那座城堡从不是我家  已经送给人民了
That castle was never my home. It was given to the people.
所以说你也是真正的公主
So, you're also a true princess.
虽然斯特凡死了  被杀了
Even though Stefan died. Was killed?
提醒我一下  他是死了还是被杀了
Remind me, did he die or was he killed?
被杀而死
Both.
你说得没错  最近是很暖和
Yes, you're right, it is very warm recently.
因为我记得一个婴儿的故事
Because I remember the story of a baby.
婴儿被施咒沉睡
A baby cursed to sleep...
再也没有醒来
and never wake up.
真的吗
Really?
谁会对无辜的孩子做这么可怕的事
Who would do such a terrible thing to an innocent child?
有很多会对无辜者下手的人
Well, there are many who prey on the innocent.
你们一族肯定会认同
I'm sure your kind would agree.
我们一族是什么意思
What do you mean, my kind?
她的意思是人类
She means humans.
摩尔王国有仙子失踪
There are fairies missing from the Moors.
我缺失的是酒
What I'm missing is some wine.
被人类偷猎者偷走
Stolen by human poachers.
这是我第一次听说
That's the first I've heard of it.
有人下了令
Someone gave the order.
听起来你在指控国王
It sounds as if you're accusing the king.
不  她没那么说
No, she never said that.
等等  不好意思  谁会偷仙子
Wait... Sorry, who would steal a fairy?
陛下  我必须上报
Your Majesty, I must report
两个平民被发现死在摩尔王国外
that two peasants were found dead... just outside the Moors.
他们失踪了好几天
They'd been missing for several days.
明白了
I see.
我们都明白了
Yes, we all see.
边境开放  但并不欢迎人类  不是吗
The borders are open, but humans are not welcome. Isn't that right?
你到底在暗示什么  陛下
What exactly are you implying, Your Majesty?
无辜人类在摩尔王国被残忍杀害
Innocent men are being slaughtered on the Moors...
她却在说仙子
and she's talking about fairies.
管好你的动物
Contain your animal.
否则我替你管
Or I will.
要不是我明事理
If I didn't know better,
我会以为你在威胁
I'd say you were making a threat.
你是吗
Well, do you?
-我是什么  -明事理
- Do I what? - Know better?
够了
Enough.
把它放下
Put her down.
拜托  把它放下
Please, put her down.
我们是来庆祝的
We're here to celebrate.
原谅我  他说得对
Forgive me, he's right.
不要忘了我们在此的原因
Let's not forget why we're here.
奥萝拉新人生的开始
The start of a new life for Aurora.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
玛琳菲森  你的付出令人钦佩
You have done an admirable job, Maleficent...
违背自己的天性抚养这个孩子
going against your own nature to raise this child.
但是现在
But now...
奥萝拉终于要得到...
Aurora will finally get...
真正家庭的爱了
the love of a real family.
一位真正的母亲
A real mother.
因为我唯一后悔的
Because the one thing I regret...
就是没有自己的女儿
is never having a daughter of my own.
但今晚改变了这点
But tonight changes that.
今晚  我把奥萝拉当亲生女儿
Tonight, I consider Aurora my own.
卫兵
Guards!
我们把女巫请进了家门
We have opened our home to a witch!
住手
Stop!
不会有结盟
There is no union.
也不会有婚礼
There will be no wedding.
-玛琳菲森  -我们必须保护国王
- Maleficent! - We must protect the king!
玛琳菲森  请你快停手
Maleficent, please, stop now.
约翰  我好害怕
John, I'm so frightened.
她对我做了什么
What has she done to me?
父亲
Father!
约翰
John!
我们回家
We go home.
约翰
John!
这是诅咒
It's a curse.
It's a curse!
玛琳菲森对国王施咒了
Maleficent has cursed the king!
你做了什么
What have you done?
我什么都没做
I've done nothing.
奥萝拉  我们立刻回家
Aurora, we go home now.
奥萝拉
Aurora!
解除诅咒
Wake him!
解除诅咒  求你了
Wake him, please.
都让开
Stand aside!
快抬到卧室
To the bedroom!
这种魔力  我们没有办法解除
This magic, we have no tools to reverse it.
一定有伤口
There must be a lesion.
她施法的证据
Proof of her witchery.
请为陛下保留些颜面吧
Please, leave His Majesty his dignity.
我们都看见玛琳菲森对他做了什么
We all saw what Maleficent did to him.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
诅咒我们的国王就是诅咒这个王国
A curse upon our king is a curse upon this kingdom.
他只是想要和平
All he wanted was peace.
这都是我的错
This is all my fault.
你完全不需要道歉  亲爱的
You have nothing to apologize for, my dear.
玛琳菲森对所有人都是威胁
Maleficent is a threat to everyone.
对你尤其如此
Especially you.
我们会尽全力保护你的
We'll do our best to protect you.
一定有办法能解除诅咒
There must be a way to reverse this.
母亲  你吻他一下试试
Mother, could you try kissing him?
真爱之类的
True love and all that.
我猜是没用的
I doubt that would work.
也许能救他呢
It could save him.
-吻就只是吻  -拜托了  母亲
- A kiss is just a kiss. - Please, Mother.
好吧
Very well.
你渴望和平
You wanted peace...
那就永远和平地安息吧
now rest in peace forever.
我早说过了
I told you.
这可不是童话
This is no fairy tale.
我必须回摩尔一趟
I have to return to the Moors.
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
等一下  过来
Wait, wait. Come here.
我必须找到她
I have to find her.
现在已经半夜了
It's the middle of the night.
她会解开诅咒的  我知道她会的
She will break the curse. I know she will.
好  那让我跟你一起去吧
Okay, well, let me come with you.
不  你应该和你的家人在一起
No. You should stay with your family.
你就是我的家人
You are my family.
让她去吧  菲利普
Let her go, Philip.
也许她可以拯救国王
Maybe she can save him.
玛琳菲森
Maleficent!
教母
Godmother!
求你回来
Please come back.
她不在摩尔境内
She's not in the Moors.
迪瓦尔
Diaval.
没有人看到过她
No one's seen her.
见到你我太高兴了
I'm so happy to see you.
哪里都找不到她
She's nowhere to be found.
如果她再也不回来怎么办
What if she never comes back?
那我就要永远保持人形了
I could be stuck as a human forever.
我必须找到她
I have to find her.
只有她能解开诅咒
She's the only one who can break the curse.
告诉我  她已经死了
Tell me she's dead.
铁珠击穿了她的身体
The iron pierced her flesh.
她掉进河里  坠下了瀑布
She fell into the river and went over the falls.
那她的头颅在哪里
Then where is her head?
出现了别的东西
There was something else.
另一个怪物
Another creature.
它把她从海底救了起来
It pulled her from the depths of the sea.
它长什么样
What did it look like?
和她一样
Her.
它抱着她飞上了天空
It carried her up into the sky.
受伤的野兽突然发狂
A wounded animal lashes out
而现在她有同伙了
and now she's not alone.
我们必须做好开战的准备
We must be ready for war.
玛琳菲森对国王施咒了
Maleficent has cursed the king!
待在室内
Stay inside!
玛琳菲森对国王施咒了
Maleficent has cursed the king!
要不是康诺尔找到她  她早没命了
If Conall hadn't found her, she would be dead.
他们想用这玩意儿杀死她
They tried to kill her with this.
你们听到了吗
Do you hear it?
这是人类发出的信号
It's a message from the humans.
我听得再清楚不过了
I hear it loud and clear.
我们生死存亡的时刻到了
Time for us to die.
几百年来  人类一直用铁来对付我们
Humans have used iron against us for centuries.
我们差点因此灭族
And we are almost extinct because of it.
屠杀摩尔的平民
Killing peasants on the Moors
只会引发更多的冲突  博拉
will only lead to more conflict, Borra.
人类从土地中挖出铁
They've pulled the iron from the earth...
做成剑和盾  把我们逼到了地底
made their swords and shields, drove us underground.
而这个
But this...
会让我们彻底灭亡
This will finish us.
我们在这里仍然安全
Our people are safe here for now.
但能维持多久呢
But for how long?
人类会找到我们  他们不会停手
The humans will find us. They will not stop.
我提议发动战争
I call for war.
I call for war!
刻不容缓
Right now!
人类的数量太多了
There are too many humans.
人类的王国太多了
Too many kingdoms.
康诺尔  人类会不停地寻找
Conall, they will keep finding
毁灭我们的新手段
new ways to destroy us.
我们赢不了
We can't win.
We can't win!
靠战争赢不了
Not this way.
不  你错了  康诺尔
No. You're wrong, Conall.
我们有他们意想不到的绝招
We have something they didn't plan on.
我们有她
We have her.
她有我们任何人都不具备的力量
She holds powers none of us possess.
她受伤了  博拉
She is wounded, Borra.
你们是谁
Who are you?
你散发着人类的恶臭
You reek of human.
也许我看错了你
Maybe I was wrong about you.
也许康诺尔应该把你留在海底
Or maybe Conall should have left you for dead
任由你死去
at the bottom of the sea.
不对
No.
它确实存在  对吗
It's there, isn't it?
它就在你体内
It's inside you.
你们看到了吗
You see?
你们看到她体内的力量了吗
You see what's inside her?
那将能拯救我们所有人
That is what will save us all.
你救了我
You saved me.
跟我来
Come.
我带你看我们是谁
Let me show you who we are.
我们是黑暗仙子
We're Dark Fey.
和你一样
Same as you.
我们是仅存的黑暗仙子了
We're all that remain.
躲藏在此处  远离人类
Unseen here, far away from mankind.
快看
Look!
当越来越多的人类王国出现
As more human kingdoms emerged,
世界各个角落的我们
we went into hiding...
不得不躲藏起来
from every corner of the earth...
为了生存竭尽全力
doing what we had to, to survive.
但我们失去了很多同伴
But many were lost.
仅仅几代仙子之前
Only a few generations ago...
我们一族遍布世界各处
our kind roamed every part of the world.
冻土平原
The tundra.
森林
The forest.
丛林
The jungle.
沙漠
The desert.
如今  我们仅存的避难所
Now, our only refuge is here...
就是这个洞穴
in this cave.
我们祖先的巢穴
Our nest of origin.
听着  去风中玩耍吧
Listen. Play in the wind.
去吧
Go!
那些孩子本该在树林和河流上方遨游
Those children should be soaring over the trees and rivers.
然而他们只能在流亡中长大
Instead, they are raised in exile.
我能保护他们
I could protect them.
怎么保护  靠跟人类开战吗
How? By waging war against the humans?
我一生都在和人类斗争
I've been at war with them my whole life.
并非所有的人类
Not all of them.
有一个人类孩子你视如己出
There was one you raised as your own.
也许我们不需要躲避人类
Maybe we don't have to hide from the humans.
也许我们能生存下去  摆脱恐惧
Maybe we can exist without fear...
摆脱战争
and war.
找到共存的办法
Find a way together.
那永远不可能实现
That will never happen.
抓到你啦
Gotcha!
欢迎来到你的新家
Welcome to your new home.
我们都很担心你  亲爱的
We've been worried about you, dear.
陛下
Your Majesty.
我找不到她
I couldn't find her.
我真为你心碎
My heart breaks for you.
她为你的幸福蒙上了一层乌云
She has brought a cloud of darkness upon your happiness.
我知道她反对这门婚事
I know she was against this marriage.
她也未曾信任过你作为女王的直觉
Never trusted your instincts as a queen.
当我在晚宴上见到她
When I saw her at dinner...
她的角被遮盖住
with her horns covered...
掩饰着扭曲
bent cowering...
是啊
Well,
她突然发狂一点也不奇怪
it's no wonder that she lashed out.
我不知道该怎么做
I just don't know what to do.
你确实很爱他  不是吗
You do truly love him, don't you?
我的儿子
My son.
我深爱着他
Deeply.
爱会治愈你
It is love that will heal you.
爱会治愈我们所有人
It's what heals us all.
让我们作为一家人
Let's move forward together...
一起向前看
as a family.
致摩尔王国的所有生灵
To all who live on the Moors...
那是什么声音
What is that noise?
以及远方的各国
...and kingdoms far and wide,
我们的国王和王后邀请你们
the king and queen invite you...
来参加他们的儿子菲利普
to attend the wedding...
和奥萝拉在三天后的婚礼
of their son Philip to Aurora in three days' time.
欢迎所有生灵
All are welcome.
所有生灵都应该到场
And all are expected!
你听到了吗  我们被邀请去城堡了
Did you hear that? We're invited to the castle!
我就知道奥萝拉不会丢下我们
I knew Aurora wouldn't abandon us!
我一直都知道自己会受邀的
I always knew I'd be invited.
很高兴你俩也能参加
Just glad you two made the cut.
谁要结婚了
Who's getting married?
奥萝拉  我们不用着急婚礼的事
Aurora, we don't have to think about the wedding right now.
王后说得对
The queen is right.
我们需要对大家有交代
We owe it to everyone...
尤其是国王
especially the king.
那玛琳菲森呢
What about Maleficent?
她已经不在了
She's gone.
凤凰
The Phoenix.
传说她是黑暗仙子的祖先
It is said the Dark Fey began with her...
经过了几个世纪的演化
evolved over centuries.
你是她最后的后裔
You are the last of her descendants.
你和她血脉相连
Her blood is your own.
你就是她
You are her.
你手中掌握着控制生死的能力
In your hands, you hold the power of life and death...
毁灭和重生
destruction and rebirth.
但自然最大的力量
But nature's greatest power
是真正蜕变的力量
is the power of true transformation.
你在抚养奥萝拉时蜕变了
You transformed when you raised Aurora.
你在痛苦中
When you found love...
找到了爱
in the middle of your pain.
我请求你把你的一切愤怒
I'm asking you to take all of your fury...
一切痛苦
all of your pain...
全部摒弃
and not use it.
帮助我们与人类和平共处
Help us broker peace with the humans.
因为和平
Because peace...
可能会是黑暗仙子最后的蜕变
could be the Dark Fey's final transformation.
摩尔王国是我们在世上最后的净土
The Moors are our last true nature on earth.
而你让一个人类当了女王
And yet you named a human as queen.
你爱护的女儿
A daughter you cared for.
我没有女儿
I have no daughter.
她已经选择了自己的立场
She has chosen her side.
我们刚刚听说
We've just heard.
三天后城堡中会举行婚礼
There's going to be a wedding at the castle in three days.
各地的人类都会过去
Humans will come from all over.
我们就在那时进攻
That's when we attack.
杀了奥斯戴的国王和王后
We'll kill the king and queen of Ulstead...
还有他们的小王子
and their young prince.
他们的王国将会灭亡
Their kingdom will fall.
仙子将再次崛起
And the Fey will rise again.
这是仙子们做的
The fairies made it.
这是我嫁给国王时穿的
I wore it when I married the king.
肯定是完美的嫁衣
I'm sure it's perfect.
我同意
So am I.
陛下  她真漂亮
Your Majesty, she's absolutely lovely.
考虑到她的身世背景
Considering how she was raised.
被那个对她施咒的邪恶女巫抚养长大
By the same evil witch who cursed her.
她能遇上菲利普王子真是奇迹
It's a miracle Prince Philip came along.
这可怜的姑娘能活下来就是奇迹了
It's a miracle the poor child is alive at all.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
太精美了
It's exquisite.
等我长大了
When I'm older...
就和你一起住在摩尔王国
I'm going to live here, in the Moors, with you.
这样我们就能相互照顾
Then we can look after each other.
-跟我说说你有什么烦心事  -没什么
- Tell me what's troubling you. - It's nothing.
奥萝拉  我了解你
Aurora, I know you better than that.
这些珠宝
This jewelry...
我的发型
my hair...
那么多规矩
all these rules.
让我喘不过气
I just... I can't breathe.
我感觉自己不再是摩尔王国的女王了
I feel like I'm not Queen of the Moors anymore.
我感觉像变了个人
I feel like a different person.
听着
Listen...
我爱上的是森林里的那个女孩  并且只爱她
I fell in love with a girl in the forest and only her.
你不必改变
You don't have to change.
我不想让你改变
I don't want you to change.
我真不该让她戴头巾
I should have never asked her to wear that scarf.
铁粉
太棒了
Ah, yes.
怎么样
Well...
成功了吗
Does it work?
我只有屈指可数的几个仙子用来试验
I only have a handful of fairy specimens to work with...
而且提取过程很艰难
and the extraction process is painstaking.
提取什么
Extraction from what?
彼岸花
Tomb Bloom flowers.
它们生长于仙子的坟墓
They grow from a fairy's grave,
含有仙子的精华
contain their very essence.
将它的花粉与铁粉混合
When you mix the pollen with iron powder...
形成的粉末能杀死仙子
the resulting dust ends a fairy's life.
我们需要几千朵彼岸花
We will need thousands more.
演示一下
Show me.
好的
Very well.
来吧
So...
摩尔王国终于是我的囊中之物了
Finally, the Moors will be mine.
仙子将不复存在
No more fairies.
保持警惕  兄弟们
Stay alert, men.
就是在这里找到的
This is where I found them.
很好
Excellent.
万一长翅膀的怪物回来怎么办
But what if the winged one returns?
用不着担心
Don't you worry about that.
我们会做好准备
We'll be ready.
去摘彼岸花吧
Take the Tomb Blooms.
动手吧
Get to work!
哨兵  保持警惕
Sentries, stay alert!
准备好武器
Keep your weapons on hand.
麻利点
Move it!
玛琳菲森
Maleficent...
我们在这里安葬死者
This is where we bury our dead.
被他们摧毁了
They've destroyed it.
人类就是这样
This is what the humans do.
他们不过是挤满大地的蝗虫
They're nothing but locusts that swarm the earth.
我们必须阻止他们
We have to stop them.
你花了很多年照顾一个人类
You spent years caring for a human...
现在该照顾你自己的同类了
now it's time to care for your own.
射击
Fire!
填弹  再来
Reload! We go again!
射击
Fire!
填弹  还有一个
Reload! There's another one!
大家跟紧点
Everyone, stay together!
我们要离开摩尔王国了
We're about to leave the Moors.
握住离你最近的手或翅膀  或尾巴
Grab the hand or the wing... or the tail of whoever is closest to you.
这边  这边
Hey, over here! Yeah, over here!
维持队形  卫兵们  维持队形
Hold formation, guards. Hold formation.
-不好意思  先生  -站住
- Excuse me, sir. - Stop right there.
我是新娘那边的
I'm with the bride.
我们奉命让怪物先就座
We've been told to let the, uh, other kind find their seats first.
但我不是人类
But I'm not a human.
-我是乌鸦  -什么
- I'm a raven. - What?
我是乌鸦  黑色的鸟
A raven. The black bird.
这米真好吃
This rice is delicious.
这是用来撒向新娘和新郎的
You're supposed to throw it at the bride and groom.
什么  浪费好好的米
What? And waste good rice?
为什么要拦着我们
What's the hold up?
让我进去
Let me in!
为什么人类不能进去
Why can't humans come in, too?
为什么我们不能进去
Why can't we come in?
我知道这样不吉利
I know it's bad luck...
但我必须见你
but I had to see you.
给你的
For you.
彼岸花
A Tomb Bloom?
你从哪里弄来的
Where did you get this?
从我母亲那里拿的
From my mother.
天亮了  今天是我们的大喜之日
The sun's up. It's our wedding day.
从我母亲那里拿的
From my mother.
我们该坐在哪里  蓝蝶仙子
Where should we sit, Flittle?
坐在左边  我们是新娘那边的
On the left. We're with the bride.
没错
Yes, we are.
但新郎也很可爱
But the groom's lovely, too.
没错
Yes, he is.
我两边都是
I'm with both.
好了
Now.
怎么回事
What's this?
除了我  谁都不许进来
Nobody is allowed in here except me.
而我已经进来了  所以赶紧出去
And I'm already here, so go away!
玛琳菲森  请你快停手
Maleficent, please stop.
玛琳菲森
Maleficent.
不是她做的
She didn't do it.
出去
Get out!
否则我叫卫兵来了
Before I call the guards!
失踪的仙子
The missing fairies.
我说了出去  你听到了吗
I said get out. Did you hear me?
你做了什么
What have you done?
你是精灵
You're a pixie.
你竟敢这么叫我
How dare you call me that?
我是贵族马屁精
I'm Lickspittle, the nobleman...
我是王后的手下
and I serve the queen.
她夺走了你的翅膀
She took your wings.
我们得放了他们
We have to release them.
他们属于摩尔王国
They belong on the Moors.
你也是  奥萝拉
As you do, Aurora.
一个背叛了同类的人类
A human who has betrayed her kind.
是你对国王施了咒
You put the curse on the king.
亲爱的
Oh, dear.
你或许是女王
You may be queen...
但你太年轻了
but you are very young.
统治人类比你头戴鲜花
Ruling humans is a bit more complicated...
赤脚到处跑要更复杂
than running around barefoot with flowers in your hair.
我年轻时
When I was young...
我娘家的王国与摩尔王国接壤
my family's kingdom bordered the Moors.
在一个异常寒冷的冬天
And one particularly harsh winter...
我们的庄稼死了
our crops died...
人民开始遭罪
and the people began to suffer.
我们的视线越过城墙
And as we looked over our walls...
看到仙子繁荣生活着
we could see the fairies thriving.
我哥哥和我认为应该夺取所需
My brother and I believed we should take what we needed...
但我的父王亲却指望着仙子的仁慈
while my father, the king, sought their kindness.
选择了和平  而不是我们的子民
Choosing peace over our people,
他派我哥哥去商议
he sent my brother to do his bidding.
但他一去不回
He never came back.
那些野蛮的
Those savages...
连话都不会说的怪物
creatures who could barely grunt,
不由分说地杀了他
let alone engage in talks, killed him.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
我们的人民开始恐惧
Our people became fearful.
他们推翻了我父王
They overthrew my father.
王国陷入混乱  我被驱逐了
The land fell into chaos. I was cast out.
命运迫使我嫁给了奥斯戴的约翰国王
Forced by fate into marriage with King John of Ulstead.
又是一个软弱的国王
Another weak king
满口包容与礼待
speaking of tolerance and civility.
现在  我的亲生儿子
And now, my own son...
也被追求和谐的幻想蒙蔽了
corrupted with visions of harmony.
但我们不会被和平毁灭
But peace will not be our downfall.
把她锁起来
Now lock her up.
战争就要来了
A war is coming.
不  不
No! No!
真希望你能出席婚礼
I wish you could be here with me.
康诺尔想要和平
Conall wanted peace...
他们却用铁攻击他
and they filled him with iron.
我们的战争要打响了
Now, we will have our war.
我们的战斗现在开始
Our fight begins now!
我们将一起崛起
We will rise together!
我们一起战斗
We fight together.
我们绝不会手下留情
And we will show them no mercy!
快点  出发
Come on! Go!
快  快
Go! Go!
快  快  快
Go! Go! Go!
菲利普的客人都在哪
Where are all Philip's guests?
人类真不守时
Humans are poor timekeepers.
开始奏乐
Start the music.
快点  快点
Come on! Come on!
她不见了
She's gone.
是陷阱  躲起来
It's a trap! Get down!
陛下
Your Majesty...
他们从海上来了
they're coming from the sea.
她逃走了
She escaped!
这边走  快点
Down this way, come on!
陛下
Your Highness.
听我指挥
Upon my command.
检查每一间屋子
Check every room!
她跑不远的
She can't be far!
等着
Wait.
怎么回事
What's going on?
发射
Now.
Fire!
不
No!
他们看起来和她一样
They look just like her.
撤退
Withdraw!
Pull back!
玛琳菲森挑起了战争
Maleficent's starting a war.
先是我父亲  现在又这样
First my father, and now this.
菲利普  她没有对他施咒
Philip! She didn't curse him.
-玛琳菲森  -什么
- Maleficent. - What?
她根本没有对他施咒
She never cursed him.
是你母亲做的
It was your mother.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
是纺锤
It was the spindle.
上面还有诅咒
The curse is still in it.
你母亲用它对付你父亲
Your mother used it against your father.
看
Look.
一模一样
It's the same.
她把摩尔居民锁在了教堂里
She's locked the Moor folk in the chapel.
这不是婚礼
This isn't a wedding.
而是陷阱
It's a trap.
记住你来自哪里
Remember where you came from.
记住你是谁
Remember who you are.
我已经做出了选择
I've made my choice.
你也得做出选择
You'll have to make yours.
飞低一点
Stay low!
散开
Divide!
跟着我
Follow me!
进攻
Attack!
-点火  -点火
- Ignite! - Ignite!
不
No!
姑母  姑母
Aunties! Aunties!
太重了
It's too heavy!
奥萝拉
Aurora!
迪亚瓦  你来了
Diaval! You're here.
怎么回事
What's happening?
换武器
Weapon change!
换武器  快
Weapon change! Go!
母亲
Mother!
你得阻止这一切
You have to stop this.
我们在打仗
We are at war.
这不是战争  这是屠杀
This isn't a war. It's a massacre.
菲利普  你不明白
Philip, you don't understand.
这些怪物阻挡我们
These creatures stand between us...
获取生存所需的资源
and everything we need to survive.
你错了
You're wrong.
我们可以共存
We can stand together.
你这个傻瓜居然真信
Well, you're a fool to believe that.
你不知道为我们的同类而战要付出什么
You don't know what it takes to fight for our kind.
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我是在保护王国
I am protecting the kingdom...
以及你的王位
and your throne.
那父亲呢
What about Father?
你也是在保护他吗
Were you protecting him, too?
王子身体不适
The prince is not feeling well.
带他回房休息
See him to his chambers.
马上
Now.
殿下  不要
Sire, stop!
停手  停手
Yield! Yield!
我母亲对国王施咒
My mother cursed the king
目的是毁灭摩尔居民
so she could destroy the Moor folk.
你的手下正在为此付出惨重代价
Your men are paying heavily for it.
我们必须做点什么
We have to do something!
再见  姐妹们
Goodbye, girls.
不  回来
No, come back!
蓝蝶仙子  不
Flittle! No!
不
No!
去跟同类待在一起
Hey, you, stay with your own!
快跑  奥萝拉  快跑
Run, Aurora, run!
放开他
Let him go!
不  不
No! No!
教母
Godmother.
为了蓝蝶仙子
For Flittle!
抓到她了
We've got her!
快跑  快跑
Go! Go!
这边  这边
This way! This way!
快跑
Go!
退下
Stand down!
我不想打这场仗
This is not my fight.
我母亲想要战争  而你让她如愿以偿
My mother wanted a war, and you're giving it to her.
我不会允许她的仇恨毁灭你我的王国
I won't allow her hatred to ruin my kingdom or yours.
我手上不会沾染仙子的血
There will be no Fey blood on my hands.
这边  这边
This way! This way!
玛琳菲森回来了
Maleficent's back!
她要去找王后
She's going for the queen.
停手  停手
Yield! Yield!
停手
Stand down!
放下武器
Lower your weapons!
我跟他们预言的恶魔出现了
There's the evil that I promised them.
你们比人类还容易预测
Your kind is more predictable than humans.
住手
Stop!
大致如此
Well, almost.
住手
Stop.
很抱歉我怀疑了你  但你不是这样的
I'm sorry I doubted you, but this isn't you.
这不是唯一的方法
There's another way.
我了解你
I know who you are.
I know you.
你不了解
You do not.
我了解
Yes, I do.
你是我母亲
You're my mother.
不
No!
你知道伟大领袖的必备条件吗  奥萝拉
Do you know what makes a great leader, Aurora?
向子民灌输恐惧的能力
The ability to instill fear in your subjects...
并且利用那种恐惧
and then use that fear...
陛下
Your Majesty.
对付你的敌人
against your enemies.
所以...
So...
我散布了那个关于邪恶女巫
I spread the story of the evil witch...
以及被她施咒的公主的故事
and the princess she cursed.
谁唤醒了睡美人并不重要
It didn't matter who woke Sleeping Beauty.
他们都吓坏了
They were all terrified.
而故事成为了传说
And the story became legend.
我知道你认为我是恶魔
I know you think I'm a monster.
但我对国王  玛琳菲森和我儿子所做的
But what I did to the king, to Maleficent, to my son...
都是为了奥斯戴王国
I did for Ulstead.
你背叛了你的同类
You are a traitor to your kind,
你要为此付出代价
and you will pay for it.
玛琳菲森已死
Maleficent is dead!
我们再也不会生活在恐惧之中了
We will never again live in fear!
回来
Get back here!
奥斯戴王国终于自由了
Ulstead is free at last!
放开我
Let me go!
怎么回事
What's happening?
看啊
Well, well.
你好  小怪物
Hello, Beasty.
我想你了
I missed you.
你撞到脑袋了吗
Did you bump your head, then?
对
I did.
菲利普
Philip.
什么
Yes?
你爱我女儿吗
Do you love my daughter?
全心全意
With everything I have.
那好
Good.
我想这个是你的
I believe this belongs to you.
诅咒是无法结束的
Curses don't end.
只能被解开
They're broken.
结束了
It ends.
不会再有战争了
There will be no more fighting.
奥斯戴再也不会进攻摩尔了
Ulstead will never attack the Moors again.
从今日起
And from this day on...
我们携手向前
we move forward...
找到前行的道路
and find our way...
共享和平
in peace.
团结一致
Together.
今天  会有一场婚礼
Today, there will be a wedding.
这不只是两个人的结合
Not just a union of two people...
更是两个王国的结合
but a union of two kingdoms.
所有人都受邀参加
And all are invited...
所有人都是安全的
all are safe...
所有人都将受到欢迎
and all are welcome.
你好呀
Hello, there.
我们不能和怪物生活在一起...
We cannot live amongst monsters...
某人真该把那对角好好藏起来
Someone should really cover those horns.
要是康诺尔能看见你就好了
If only Conall could see you.
博拉
Borra...
是时候回家了
it's time to come home.
你们好
Hello.
你能过来一下吗
Can you come here?
怎么了
Yes?
你愿意把我送出去吗
Will you give me away?
绝不
Never.
不是
No.
你愿意送我出嫁吗
Will you walk me down the aisle?
愿意
Yes.
向所有今天被我伤到的人道歉
Apologies to anyone I might have mauled today.
那是...
Is that...?
她能把她变回去的
She can change her back.
应该能
I suppose.
得我们愿意才行
Only if we wanted to.
父亲
Father.
很高兴见到你
I'm so glad to see you.
我一直梦想着这一刻
I've dreamed of this moment.
两个王国终于团结一致
Two kingdoms united at last.
而这都多亏了你
And it's because of you.
我太为你感到骄傲了  太骄傲了
I'm so proud of you. So proud.
她穿绿色更好看
She looks better in green.
你是说粉色吧
Pink, you mean.
不  绿色
No, in green.
粉色
Pink.
-绿色  -粉色
- Green. - Pink.
蓝蝶仙子
Flittle!
太完美了
It's perfect.
放手吧
Let her go.
你振作一点
Pull yourself together.
我们在此联合两个王国
We are here to join two kingdoms...
它们曾因恐惧而生嫌隙
divided by fear.
今天  你们教会了我们
Today, you teach us
我们是谁并非取决于我们来自哪里
we are not defined by where we are from...
而是取决于我们爱的是谁
but by whom we love.
戒指  谢谢
The bands, please.
菲利普  你愿意娶奥萝拉...
Do you, Philip, take Aurora...
我愿意
I do.
奥萝拉  你愿意...
And do you, Aurora, take...
我愿意
I do.
我宣布你们结为夫妻
Then I pronounce you husband and wife.
你可以亲吻新娘了
You may kiss the bride.
你在微笑
You're smiling.
新的一天到来了
It's a new day.
是啊
It is.
早上好
Morning.
你会多待一阵子吗
Will you stay awhile?
一小阵子
A little while.
但别担心
But don't worry...
我会来参加洗礼的
I'll see you at the christening.
You Can't Stop The Girl - Bebe Rexha
♪ Oh ,they tryna shoot down angels ♪
♪ They tryna pull their wings off ♪
♪ So they can't fly ♪
♪ And, oh ♪
♪ But she's so brave, though ♪
♪ Just like a tornado ♪
♪ She's taking us by storm ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl from going ♪
♪ You can't stop the world from knowing ♪
♪ The truth will set you free ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl from going ♪
♪ You can't stop the world from knowing ♪
♪ The truth will set you free ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl ♪
♪ They tryna take our voices ♪
♪ They tryna make our choices ♪
♪ So we scream loud, loud, loud ♪
♪ And, oh ♪
♪ I know you feel the lightnin' ♪
♪ And it's so excitin' ♪
♪ So, here we come ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl from going ♪
♪ You can't stop the world from knowing ♪
♪ The truth will set you free ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl from going ♪
♪ You can't stop the world from knowing ♪
♪ The truth will set you free ♪
♪ You can't stop the girl ♪
♪ No, you can't stop the girl ♪
♪ Oh, I know you feel the lightnin' ♪
♪ And it's so excitin' ♪
♪ So, here we come. ♪